Oh, Gary.
哦，加里。
Come outside.
到外面来吧。
I've got a surprise for you.
我给你准备了一个惊喜。
You're gonna love this, Gary,
really love it.
你一定会喜欢这个的，加里，
真的很喜欢它。
You ready?
你准备好了吗？
Ta-da!
It's a playhouse just for you.
哒哒！
这是一个只适合你的游乐场。
Now you're a homeowner
just like me,
现在你是房主了
就像我一样，
minus the mortgage payments.
减去抵押贷款。
Blah!
废话！
Go on.
继续。
Go right in.
向右进去。
Meow.
喵。
Don't you love it?
你不喜欢它吗？
♪ Who lives in a playhouse
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在剧场里
在海底？ ♪
- Meow.
- That's right. You.
- 喵。
- 这是正确的。你。
Well, I'm gonna leave you alone
to play.
好吧，我会让你一个人呆着
玩。
Have fun.
- Mwah!
玩得开心。
- 哇！
Gary, time to come in.
加里，该进来了。
Gary?
Gare-bear?
加里？
车站熊？
Meow?
喵？
Come on, buddy. It's late.
Time to go inside.
来吧，伙计。现在已经晚了。
是时候进去了。
No?
不？
You wanna spend the night
in your new playhouse?
你想过夜
在你的新剧场里？
Aww,
that is so cu--
哇哦，
真是太可爱了--
Hmm.
唔。
Where'd he get a door?
他哪里来的门？
Okay.
好的。
Well, I'm--I'm really happy
you like my gift.
嗯，我真的很高兴
你喜欢我的礼物。
Okay, well, good night.
好吧，晚安。
SpongeBob,
will you knock off that racket?
海绵宝宝，
你会停止那个喧嚣吗？
It's not me.
这不是我。
What?
什么？
It's not me.
It's Gary.
这不是我。
是加里。
Larry? That lousy lobster.
拉里？那个恶心的龙虾。
Larry, you meat head.
拉里，你这个肉头。
Whatever you're doing, stop it.
无论你在做什么，停下来。
I need my sleep.
我需要睡眠。
Uh. Uh-uh-uh.
呃。呃呃呃。
Eee!
哎呀！
Wow.
哇。
Gary, did you do this?
加里，这是你做的吗？
Uh, Gary?
呃，加里？
Huh.
呵呵。
What?
什么？
Ohhh.
This is so cute.
噢。
这太可爱了。
Gary.
- Meow.
加里.
- 喵。
Ohhhh.
哦哦。
This is too cute.
这也太可爱了吧。
I'm having a cuteness attack.
我正在遭受可爱攻击。
Oh, hi, Spot.
哦，嗨，斯波。
Meow.
喵。
Oh, that is the cutest thing
I've ever seen.
哦，这是最可爱的事情
我曾经见过。
It's so cute.
I can't breathe.
真是太可爱了。
我无法呼吸。
I need water.
我需要水。
It's too cute. It's too cute.
太可爱了。太可爱了。
Too cute. Too cute. Too cute.
太可爱了。太可爱了。太可爱了。
That garbage can
looks like Squidward's house.
那个垃圾桶
看起来像章鱼哥的房子。
Aw.
That Squidward-looking urchin
噢。
那个长得像章鱼哥的顽童
must be one of Gary's pals.
一定是加里的朋友之一。
Can this day get
any more adorable?
这一天能得到吗
还有更可爱的吗？
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Oh, it can now.
哦，现在可以了。
Get your trash can
off my--oh!
拿起你的垃圾桶
关掉我的——哦！
Hi, Squidward.
嗨，章鱼哥。
Huh?
啊？
What the?
什么？
Ew, it looks just like
that moron.
呃，看起来就像
那个白痴。
What's that?
Is that supposed to be me?
那是什么？
那应该是我吗？
Oh, that's... that's...
噢，那是……那是……
the cutest thing
I've ever seen.
最可爱的东西
我曾经见过。
It's too cute.
太可爱了。
Ohh!
哦！
- Oh-oh, oh, it's cute.
- Oh, it's too cute.
- 哦哦哦，真可爱。
- 哦，太可爱了。
- Cute, cute, cute.
- So adorable.
- 可爱，可爱，可爱。
- 太可爱了。
Adorable.
可爱的。
- Oh-ho-ho.
- That's just too much.
- 哦嗬嗬。
- 这实在是太多了。
- Oh, it's so cute.
- Too cute.
- 哦，太可爱了。
- 太可爱了。
Oh, so cute.
噢，真可爱。
What are we
blubbering about?
我们是什么
哭诉什么？
Oh, so cute.
Oh, cutie cutie cute.
噢，真可爱。
哦，可爱可爱可爱。
Ohh!
- So sweet.
哦！
- 如此甜蜜。
- So cute.
- So adorable.
- 太可爱了。
This is the cutest day ever
这是有史以来最可爱的一天
in the history
of cutest days ever.
历史上
有史以来最可爱的日子。
- Adorable.
- Too cute.
- 可爱。
- 太可爱了。
Too, too, too, too cute.
太、太、太、太可爱了。
Too, too, cute.
- Adorable.
太、太可爱了。
- 可爱。
- Precious.
- Adorable.
- 宝贵的。
- 可爱。
La-da-dee, la-de-dum,
la-da-dooo ♪
拉-达-迪，拉-德-杜姆，
拉达杜 ♪
Ahh-ahh!
啊啊啊！
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
哦-嗬-嗬-嗬。
Hey, our kids
are harassing my kid.
嘿，我们的孩子们
正在骚扰我的孩子。
They're just playing a game.
他们只是在玩游戏。
Yeah, and we're winning.
是的，我们正在获胜。
Ahh!
啊！
This is a game?
这是游戏？
both: Yay!
两人：耶！
What? What happened?
什么？发生了什么？
Nothing. We're just rooting
for our team.
没有什么。我们只是扎根
对于我们的团队。
Yay, team us.
耶，我们组队吧。
Boo, team you.
嘘，组队吧。
Maybe you should lay off
the sodas.
也许你应该休息一下
苏打水。
You've had enough sugar
for today.
你已经吃够糖了
今天。
Fine.
美好的。
Arrgh.
啊啊。
One sugar cookie ice cream
on a sugar cone, please,
一份糖饼干冰淇淋
请在甜筒上，
with extra sugar sprinkles.
撒上额外的糖。
Ohh.
哦。
Meow, meow.
喵，喵。
Duuuuh, duuuuh.
嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟。
Meow, meow.
喵，喵。
Duuuuh, duuuuh.
嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟。
Meow, meow.
喵，喵。
Good night, Patrick.
晚安，帕特里克。
Good night, SpongeBob.
晚安，海绵宝宝。
Good night, Patrick.
晚安，帕特里克。
Good night, SpongeBob.
晚安，海绵宝宝。
Good night, Patrick.
晚安，帕特里克。
Will you two please shut up?
请你们两个闭嘴好吗？
Mmm.
嗯。
Knock it off.
把它关掉。
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
Where were you two yesterday?
你们两个昨天在哪里？
I had to manage,
run the register,
我必须管理，
运行寄存器，
and cook all day
all by meself.
并整天做饭
都是我自己。
Here ya go.
给你。
Ohh!
哦！
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
热，热，热，热。
Have you ever had
to handle hot change?
你有过吗
处理热变化？
Sorry, Mr. Krabs.
对不起，蟹老板。
I guess we got carried away
我想我们得意忘形了
watching our animal
double-gaggers all day.
看着我们的动物
整天双嘴。
That's doppelgangers.
这就是双体啊
No, I believe
it's pronounced bubble hangers.
不，我相信
这就是明显的气泡衣架。
What are you barnacle brains
blabbering about?
你是什么藤壶脑
胡言乱语？
What in Neptune's creation
is that?
海王星的创造物是什么
是吗？
Ooh, and why is it so adorable?
哦哦，为什么这么可爱呢？
Scooch over.
滚过来。
Whoo-hoo. Go, Krabsy.
呼呼。走吧，克拉布西。
Oh,
a tiny little Krusty Krab.
哦，
一个小小的蟹堡王。
Yeah.
是的。
Too cute. Too cute.
太可爱了。太可爱了。
Too cute. Too cute. Too cute.
太可爱了。太可爱了。太可爱了。
Oh, boy. What's next?
哦，男孩。接下来怎么办？
I gotta know.
我必须知道。
Aw,
an adorable tour group.
噢，
一个可爱的旅行团。
Hungry. Hungry. Hungry.
饥饿的。饥饿的。饥饿的。
Hungry. Hungry.
饥饿的。饥饿的。
Huh? Ahh!
啊？啊！
Ahh!
啊！
Ooh,
I think I've seen this one.
哦，
我想我见过这个。
I think I lived this one.
我想我就是这样生活的。
This was where me boy-o
really came through.
这就是我的地方，男孩-o
真的挺过来了。
My shining moment.
我的闪亮时刻。
Eee-eee-eee.
呃-呃-呃。
- Huh?
- I don't remember this part.
- 啊？
- 我不记得这部分了。
Meow.
喵。
Meow, meow, meow, meow.
喵，喵，喵，喵。
Ahh.
啊。
Meow, meow, meow, meow.
喵，喵，喵，喵。
Huh. I guess there's
only room for one me.
呵呵。我猜有
只容我一个人住。
Or me.
或者我。
both: Or us.
两人：或者我们。
Nice to have you
back inside, Gary.
很高兴有你
回到里面，加里。
Meow.
喵。
Oh, it's nice to have you two
here as well.
哦，很高兴有你们两个
这里也一样。
Aw. Too cute. Too cute.
Too cute. Too cute!
噢。太可爱了。太可爱了。
太可爱了。太可爱了！